# SARA MICHELLE OUELLET

289-387-0189

saraouellet13@hotmail.com

#### Profile

I am an experienced Visual leader, specializing in branding and customer experience.

I balance my creative instinct with analytical research to reinforce my decisions and solve design problems to reduce friction.

My natural empathy for the visitor has been pivotal in my career thus far.

#### Education

CareerFoundry UX Immersion 2018-2019

Seneca College Visual Merchandising Arts 2012-2014

### Skills

- Adobe Photoshop, Illustrator, InDesign and XD
- HTML, CSS, Java
- Invision, Balsamiq, Sketch
- MicrosoftOffice
- Business management
- multi-level project management
- Fluent in French

## Experience

Visual Merchandising Manager (Flagship) URBN 2015 - present

Regional Visual Merchandiser Mendocino

2014-2015

Visual Merchandiser

Kate Spade 2013-2014

## Responsibilities

- omni channel marketing
- market and customer research
- leading and developing creative team
- executing retail programs in alignment with brand messages
- KPI analysis and ROI metrics
- traffic flow mapping
- creating design strategies as solutions for pain points
- ensuring a frictionless experience for visitors
- ensuring cohesive messagesfor easy self service
- implementing visual strategies while maintaining focus on business goals